{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the only food that cannot go bad?",
      "option_a": "Dark chocolate",
      "option_b": "Peanut butter",
      "option_c": "Canned tuna",
      "option_d": "Honey",
      "correct_answer": "Honey",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which was René Magritte’s first surrealist painting?",
      "option_a": "Not to Be Reproduced",
      "option_b": "Personal Values",
      "option_c": "The Lovers",
      "option_d": "The Lost Jockey",
      "correct_answer": "The Lost Jockey",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most visited tourist attraction in the world?",
      "option_a": "Eiffel Tower",
      "option_b": "Statue of Liberty",
      "option_c": "Great Wall of China",
      "option_d": "Colosseum",
      "correct_answer": "Eiffel Tower",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s the name of Hagrid’s pet spider?",
      "option_a": "Nigini",
      "option_b": "Crookshanks",
      "option_c": "Aragog",
      "option_d": "Mosag",
      "correct_answer": "Aragog",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s the heaviest organ in the human body?",
      "option_a": "Brain",
      "option_b": "Liver",
      "option_c": "Skin",
      "option_d": "Heart",
      "correct_answer": "Liver",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Who made the third most 3-pointers in the Playoffs in NBA history?",
      "option_a": "Kevin Durant",
      "option_b": "JJ Reddick",
      "option_c": "Lebron James",
      "option_d": "Kyle Korver",
      "correct_answer": "Lebron James",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these EU countries does not use the euro as its currency?",
      "option_a": "Poland",
      "option_b": "Denmark",
      "option_c": "Sweden",
      "option_d": "All of the above",
      "correct_answer": "All of the above",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "question": "What element does the chemical symbol Au stand for?",
      "option_a": "Silver",
      "option_b": "Magnesium",
      "option_c": "Salt",
      "option_d": "Gold",
      "correct_answer": "Gold",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the highest-grossing Broadway show of all time?",
      "option_a": "The Lion King",
      "option_b": "Wicked",
      "option_c": "Kinky Boots",
      "option_d": "Hamilton",
      "correct_answer": "The Lion King",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "On average, how many seeds are located on the outside of a strawberry?",
      "option_a": "100",
      "option_b": "200",
      "option_c": "400",
      "option_d": "500",
      "correct_answer": "200",
      "answered_correctly": false,
      "checked": false,
      "id": 10
    }
  ]
}